♪♪ Gotta get that ♪♪
♪♪ Gotta get that-- that-- that
that-- that♪♪
♪♪ Boom boom boom ♪♪
♪♪ Gotta get that ♪♪
- ♪♪ Boom boom boom ♪♪
- ♪♪ Gotta get that ♪♪
♪♪ Boom boom boom
That boom boom boom ♪♪
- ♪♪ That ♪♪
- ♪♪ Boom boom boom, boom boom ♪
♪♪ Yo, I got that hit
that beat the block ♪♪
♪♪ You can get that bass
on below ♪♪
♪♪ I got that rock and roll♪
♪♪ That future flow ♪♪
♪♪ That digital spit
Next-level visual ♪♪
♪♪ I got that boom boom boom
How the beat bang ♪♪
♪♪ Boom boom boom ♪♪
♪♪ I like
that boom boom pow ♪♪
♪♪ Them chickens
jockin' my style ♪♪
♪♪ They try to copy
my swagger ♪♪
♪♪ I'm on
that next s--- now ♪♪
♪♪ I'm so 3008 ♪♪
♪♪ You so 2000-and-late ♪♪
♪♪ I got that boom boom boom ♪♪
♪♪ That future boom boom boom ♪♪
- ♪♪ Lemme get it now ♪♪
- ♪♪ Boom boom boom ♪♪
♪♪ Gotta get that ♪♪
♪♪ Boom boom boom ♪♪
- ♪♪ Gotta get that ♪♪
- ♪♪ Boom boom boom ♪♪
♪♪ Gotta get that ♪♪
♪♪ Boom boom boom ♪♪
- ♪♪ That ♪♪
- ♪♪ Boom boom boom ♪♪
♪♪ That boom boom boom ♪♪
♪♪ Boom boom boom ♪♪
♪♪ I'm on that supersonic boom ♪
♪♪ Y'all hear
that spaceship zoom ♪♪
♪♪ When-When I step inside
the room ♪♪
♪♪ Them girls
go ape-ape, uh ♪♪
♪♪ Y'all stuck on super-e-eight♪
♪♪ That lo-fi's stupid-8
Bi--- ♪♪
♪♪ I'm on that H.D. flat ♪♪
♪♪ This be go boom boom pat♪
♪♪ I'm a beast
when you turn me on ♪♪
♪♪ Into the future
cybertron ♪♪
♪♪ Harder, faster
better, stronger ♪♪
♪♪ Sexy ladies
extra longer ♪♪
♪♪ 'Cause we got the beat
that bounce ♪♪
♪♪ We got the beat
that pounce ♪♪
♪♪ We got the beat that 808
the boom boom in your town ♪♪
♪♪ People in the place ♪♪
♪♪ If you wanna get down ♪♪
♪♪ Put your hands in the air ♪♪
♪♪ Will.i.am, drop the beat now♪
♪♪ Yo, yo, yo ♪♪
♪♪ I be rockin' them beats ♪
♪♪ Y-Yo
I be rockin' them beats ♪♪
♪♪ Yup-Yup, yup, yup
Hah, hah, hah ♪♪
♪♪ Here we go, here we go
Satellite radio ♪♪
- ♪♪ Y'all get hit with the♪
- ♪♪ Boom boom ♪♪
♪♪ Beat's so big
I'm steppin' on leprechauns ♪♪
- ♪♪ Y'all get hit with the♪
- ♪♪ Boom boom ♪♪
- ♪♪ Hip get hit with the ♪♪
- Y'all get hit with the ♪♪
- [ Beat Thumping ]
♪♪ This beat be bumpin'
Bumpin' ♪♪
♪♪ This beat go boom boom ♪♪
♪♪ Let the beat rock ♪♪
♪♪ L-L-Let the beat
r-r-rock ♪♪
♪♪ Let the beat rock ♪♪
♪♪ This beat be bumpin, bumpin'
This beat go boom boom ♪♪
♪♪ I like
that boom boom pow ♪♪
♪♪ Them chickens
jockin' my style ♪♪
♪♪ They try to copy
my swagger ♪♪
♪♪ I'm on
that next s--- now ♪♪
♪♪ I'm so 3008
You so 2000-and-late ♪♪
♪♪ I got that boom boom boom ♪♪
♪♪ That future boom boom boom
Lemme get it now ♪♪
♪♪ Boom boom boom ♪♪
♪♪ Gotta get that ♪♪
- ♪♪ Boom boom boom ♪♪
- ♪♪ Gotta get that ♪♪
♪♪ Boom boom boom ♪♪
♪♪ Gotta get that ♪♪
- ♪♪ Boom boom boom ♪♪
- ♪♪ Gotta get that ♪♪
♪♪ Boom boom boom ♪♪
- ♪♪ That ♪♪
- ♪♪ Boom boom boom ♪♪
♪♪ Boom boom boom ♪♪♪